Shaily Sutaria

UI/UX Designer

- Designer specialized at conceptualizing and producing high quality, responsive, user-centered design deliverables in agile and interactive
 development environment and understand intricate business problems, articulate complex ideas and strategies and sketch them on
 whiteboard and with tools to quickly turn ideas into prototypes.
- Have worked hand-in-hand with product, marketing, development, sales and customer success team for driving new development and improving existing features.



Contact

Phone

951-525-2860

E-mail

shah.shaily22@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/shailysutaria-8391351

Portfolio

http://shailysutaria.info/



Software

Adobe Illustrator	
Adobe Photoshop	•••00
Adobe Sketch	•••00
Adobe Spark	•••00
HTML5	••••
CSS	•••00
JavaScript	••000



Skills

Business strategy	••••
User Experience (UX)	•••00
User Interface	•••00
Design process	•••00
Product design	•••00
Product development	••000
Sales	
Sketching	•••00
Prototyping	•••00
Wireframe	••••



Education

2019-04 -Current

UI/UX And Web Design

UC Santa Cruz - Santa Clara, CA, GPA: 3.6

 Coursework in Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Sketch, HTML5 Fundamentals, Advanced HTML5 & JavaScript APIs and User Experience design fundamentals

2006-01 -2011-01

Masters And Bachelors: Commerce

Gujarat University - Ahmedabad, GPA 3.8



Work History

2019-08 -2019-12

Associate

Chico's, Palo Alto, CA

- Helped in meeting company sales goals by utilizing sales techniques and communicating product knowledge to the customer; recommends merchandise selections or helps to locate or obtain merchandise based on customer needs and desires.
- Participated in visual directives including monthly store sets and zone maintenance.
- Ensured a fast and efficient register experience, remaining current on policies regarding payments, coupon acceptance, returns and exchanges and security practices.
- Assisted with visual directives, including floor sets, window changes, visual presentations, signage placement, etc. as directed.

2008-04 -2018-12

Co-founder and CEO (Lead Fashion Designer)

Shails & Pals

- Co-founded company and lead team of 10-15 people to serve more than 500 customers across globe for more than 10 years.
- Managed entire product design process, from initial market research to mood board creation to sketching/designing to delivering end product.
- Oversaw technical designs of products from concept to factory, incl. fabric and trim selection, meeting and selecting vendors, etc.

2007-05 -2008-04

Associate Fashion Designer

Resham Dresses

- Created commercial designs that reflected the conceptual direction and business strategy of the company.
- Collaborated and followed-up on deliverables with vendors and key partners throughout the entire design process, incl. merchandising, preproduction, and product development.

2007-01 -2007-03

Trainee (Fashion Designer)

Roops Enterprise

 Participated in the production and design training and on color matching for quality control.